interworx.com 2008-05-27

# Our Privacy Policy | InterWorx Control Panel

We have authored this privacy policy so you, our clients, know what information is gathered as you browse our site and when you order and why we gather such information. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy please e-mail privacy@nexcess.net or call 1.866.NEXCESS. 

## Information Collection and Use

NEXCESS.NET, L.L.C. (”NEXCESS.NET”) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. NEXCES.NET collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

## Order

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer.s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user.s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user.s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use these same log files to generate our usage report for your site if you are one of our current clients. 

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we NEXCESS.NET are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

## Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users. information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just .surfing.. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users. information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers. information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to security@nexcess.net. 

## Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone. 

## Correction / Updating Personal Information

If a user.s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user.s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by e-mailing support@nexcess.net. 

## Choice / Opt-out

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
